[{"id":1,"user_id":1,"session_id":1,"word_prompt":"star","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2284,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:09:32.617879"},{"id":2,"user_id":1,"session_id":1,"word_prompt":"bicycle","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2900,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:09:39.900506"},{"id":3,"user_id":1,"session_id":1,"word_prompt":"circle","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2105,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:09:46.877873"},{"id":4,"user_id":1,"session_id":1,"word_prompt":"bicycle","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2983,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:09:54.597645"},{"id":5,"user_id":1,"session_id":1,"word_prompt":"bicycle","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2858,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:10:01.848643"},{"id":6,"user_id":1,"session_id":2,"word_prompt":"cat","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":3271,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:11:49.694074"},{"id":7,"user_id":1,"session_id":2,"word_prompt":"cat","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2122,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:11:55.360915"},{"id":8,"user_id":1,"session_id":2,"word_prompt":"cat","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2004,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:12:00.827959"},{"id":9,"user_id":1,"session_id":2,"word_prompt":"square","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2140,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:12:08.244545"},{"id":10,"user_id":1,"session_id":2,"word_prompt":"giraffe","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2529,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:12:17.434144"},{"id":11,"user_id":1,"session_id":3,"word_prompt":"heart","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2160,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:19:12.486546"},{"id":12,"user_id":1,"session_id":3,"word_prompt":"giraffe","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2356,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:19:22.060561"},{"id":13,"user_id":1,"session_id":3,"word_prompt":"dog","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":3010,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:19:29.068221"},{"id":14,"user_id":1,"session_id":3,"word_prompt":"castle","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2772,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:19:37.235002"},{"id":15,"user_id":1,"session_id":3,"word_prompt":"elephant","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2373,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:19:45.791198"},{"id":16,"user_id":1,"session_id":4,"word_prompt":"giraffe","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2501,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:33:59.643853"},{"id":17,"user_id":1,"session_id":4,"word_prompt":"castle","difficulty":"HARD","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2347,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:34:07.828431"},{"id":18,"user_id":1,"session_id":4,"word_prompt":"heart","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2181,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:34:14.534623"},{"id":19,"user_id":1,"session_id":4,"word_prompt":"star","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2229,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:34:20.646695"},{"id":20,"user_id":1,"session_id":4,"word_prompt":"square","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2446,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:34:28.407756"},{"id":21,"user_id":1,"session_id":5,"word_prompt":"square","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2732,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:39:13.464224"},{"id":22,"user_id":1,"session_id":5,"word_prompt":"dog","difficulty":"MEDIUM","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2921,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:39:19.542682"},{"id":23,"user_id":1,"session_id":5,"word_prompt":"circle","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2335,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:39:26.314555"},{"id":24,"user_id":1,"session_id":5,"word_prompt":"square","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":2378,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:39:34.213292"},{"id":25,"user_id":1,"session_id":5,"word_prompt":"star","difficulty":"EASY","is_correct":true,"drawing_time_ms":3561,"recognition_accuracy":1,"created_at":"2025-04-12 14:39:42.445701"}]